# SARAH GANS

## **DEVELOPER ANALYST**

sarahgans.com | https://github.com/sarahmgans | (437) 777-7348 | sarahmgans@gmail.com

## **PROFILE**

I'm Sarah, a developer analyst based in Toronto, Ontario. As a former classical cellist, I use my creativity alongside my high attention to detail in order to work effectively both independently and as part of a team. I prioritize the value of a positive customer experience, and am committed to providing the necessary insights as to enable and support data-driven decisions.

#### **SKILLS**

JavaScript	Adobe Analytics	ES6	React	A/B Test Reporting
Node.js	SQL	HTML5	Mongo DB	Firebase Realtime Database

Adobe Launch RESTful APIs CSS3/SASS Git/GitHub Google Data Studio

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Analytics and Implementation Prime | TELUS Digital | 2020 - present

- I define KPIs, design technical documentation, configure conversion variables/implement marketing pixels using JavaScript, and lead the Quality Assurance process.
- I use the data collected through this implementation process to build out reports in Adobe Analytics/Google Data Studio, analyze these reports and draw insights, visualize these insights through Google Slides, and present these slides to both technical and non-technical stakeholders.

# Assistant Principal Cello | Kitchener - Waterloo Symphony | 2016 - 2019

- I led the cello section in more than 250 performances for audiences of up to 2000 people per performance.
- I communicated and collaborated with the members of the orchestra in daily rehearsals, in addition to extensive independent daily practice, in order to be prepared for a new concert program each week.

## **EDUCATION**

Juno College of Technology | 2019 - 2020 Full-Stack Development | Web Development Bootcamp | JavaScript

The Juilliard School | 2014 - 2016 Master of Music in Cello Performance